<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UVC_Camera</string>
    <string name="readme"><![CDATA[
       
Camera stream over Usb.\n
OTG cabel or OTG Hub needed\n
It works with Micro Usb and Usb Type C devices\n
(Some OTG cabels doesn\'t work --> I\'ll found one which is an extern powered more Port USB-C OTG cable and doesn\'t work ...)\n
All phones, tablets with all chipsets are supported\n\n

Explaination:\n
To set up the userspace driver for your USB camera you have to set the following \'isochronous data transfer\' values:\n\n

Alt-Setting, Maximal-Packet-Size, Format-Index, Frame-Index, Videoformat, Image-Width, Image-Hight, Frame-Interval, Packets-Per-Request, Active-Urbs\n
This Values are explained at the end of this Text.\n\n

To adjust this values automatically, click on the Button: "SET UP WITH UVC SETTINGS". (you need a UVC compliance camera)\n
You can save your settings and restore them later, for faster setup.\n\n

To adjust this values by hand, click on the Button: "EDIT / SAVE THE CAMERA VALUES". (you need a UVC compliance camera)\n
You can save your settings and restore them later, for faster setup.\n\n

On first Start follow these steps:\n

Use the "SET UP THE CAMERA DEVICE" button --> Search for a camera.\n
Next you can list the interfaces and endpoints of the camera. (List the camera button)\n
Set up the Camera with the values for the isochronous data transfer.\n


Next important part is the Testrun for your camera.\n
Thirst you have to perform a controlltransfer.
Click "Testrun" --> "Controltransfer" --> "and perform the first Controltransfer.\n
If the controlltransfer was sucessful, you can read out one frame. The frame will be displayed below.\n
Next you can Read out all the frames for 5 secounds.\n
Have a look at your frames: If they are all identically and big enougth, than you can proceed to start the camera stream with the "Start the camera stream" button from the main screen.\n\n
Otherwise you have to edit some values for your camera: Perhaps -PacketsPerRequest- or -ActiveUrbs-, or something else.\n\n
Click the "Transmission Start" --> "Start the Camera" Button to start the transmission.\n
If everything works, you can watch the video of your camera.\n\n

Alt-Setting:\n
The Alt-Setting is a camera specific setting which defines which interface of your camera shall be used for the isochronous data transfer.\n\n

Maximal-Packet-Size:\n
Each Alt-Setting has it's own Maximal-Packet-Size. The Maximal-Packet-Size is byte Number which defines how many bytes each Packet of the iso transfer maximal contains.\n\n

Format-Index:\n
Your Camera can support different Format Index\'s. This could be MJPEG, or uncompressed (YUV) or ...\n\n

Videoformat\n
This is a helper value, which has to be set to your selected Format-Index. You have to enter YUV, or MJPEG, or ...\n\n

Frame-Index:\n
Each Format-Index of your camera can have different Frame Index\'s. This is a number which represents the camera resolution (1920x1020, or 640x480)\n\n

Image-Width, Image-Hight:\n
This are helper values, which have to be set to your selected Frame-Index. For Example: Image-Width = 640 and Image-Hight = 480\n\n

Frame-Interval:\n
The Frame-Interval is a number which defines, on how much nano secounds each new frame will be sent from the camera to your device.\n
For example: 666666 means each 0,066 Secounds a frame is sent. 666666 = 15 frames per secound.\n
333333 are 30 Frames per secound\n\n

Packets-Per-Request:\n
This is a value wich defines how many Packet will be sent from your camera to your device in one cycle of the transfer.\n\n

Active-Urbs:\n
And this value defines have many cycles are running paralell to each other in the data steam between camera and Android device.\n\n

This program is on GitHub on following link:\n
https://github.com/Peter-St/Android-UVC-Camera/

    ]]></string>
</resources>
